# **David Hesketh**

1/2, 6 Ratho Drive Mob: 07936272651

Glasgow Email: brokenbriken@gmail.com

G21 1NA GitHub: https://github.com/Briken

## **Personal Statement**

Intelligent, Game Development Graduate from Glasgow Caledonian University. Six years' experience working in my family owned vets as a clerical assistant. Extensive programming experience in C++ and C#, developing games and phone apps using visual studio integrated development environment and the Unity3D game engine. Experience with JavaScript and Visual Basic, in the development of academic and personal projects in the past year. With additional experience working with CSS and HTML in an academic context. I have spent much of the summer working with Java to develop a variety of projects and broaden my knowledge.

# **Education**

# 2014 to July 2018

BSc with 2:1 Honours: Computer Games Development (Software Development), Glasgow Caledonian

Graduate of the MThree Alumni IT Consultant training course for Financial Technologies 2018

## 2008 - 14

Advanced Highers: Computing(C)

Highers: Computing (B), Mathematics (B), English (B), Modern Studies (C), Physics (D)

## **Relevant Skills**

Software Development:

Lead developer of Bright Void, available on Google Play. Extensive knowledge and experience with the Unity Game Development Engine, from the creation of full 3D first person shooters to 2D platformers to a development project modelled after Minecraft. Minor experience with Unreal Game Development Engine in a game jam context. Experience with the development of apps in visual studio integrated development environment, including use of OpenGL and GLU libraries, specifically to aid in the development of a games engine for a games and graphics programming modules in my course. Worked with android development studio in JavaScript for the development of a 2D wave-based shooter made in the style of the classic game, "Duck Hunt". Developed a variety of coursework's in Java, notably the use of the factory pattern to determine an appropriate soring algorithm and a benchmarked algorithm for the top 3 words from a book problem in both multithreaded and non-multithreaded versions.

Linux and Bash

Skills:

Strong knowledge of Bash scripting using RedHat enterprise. I have made use of netstat, ps, awk, grep, sed, vi and ln in the creation of a coursework. This script determines the tree of child and ancestor processes for a given process up to 3 generations and for each process display the command and associated network connections.

Team-work:

My university course and current employment has required team-based work with a variety of individuals of different skill sets, levels of experience and cultural backgrounds. As a result, I can take direction effectively and voice opinions in a respectful and coherent manner and when necessary give direction to those who require it.

Communication

Skills:

Developed working in Arvato Financial Solutions over the past three years as a collections agent. In this capacity I have been working in the financial sector to collect outstanding debt and aid in dispute resolution where disputes arise. These skills have enhanced my ability to effectively communicate with those who may not have English as a first language or who may require explicit or careful explanation of complicated concepts.

# **Relevant Work Experience**

01/06/2015 – 28/06/2018

Part Time Collections Agent at Arvato Financial Solutions, working to target based collections and ensuring high quality of call through regular call monitoring and quality assurance training. Have been provided training in use of Eon Energy's ICE and Collect systems and the Caseflow Collections recording system.

June 2012 – Current:

Work experience as a clerical assistant, this has taught several skills such as to balance a till, how to take payments politely and quickly and how to do basic date-based filing in both digital and hard copy.

Summer 2013:

I did student work experience in the global business Exterity designing and implementing long-term and short-term tests for their IPTV systems. I learned quickly how their systems operated and carried out all responsibilities in an efficient and timely manner.

## **Achievements and Interests**

- Finalist in the Ford Smart Mobility Challenge and winner of one thousand euros, for the design concept "E.C.O Saviour"
- Completed the Engineering Visions Intensive Program 2017 in Trollhattan Sweden
- Lead Developer of Bright Void (available: https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.BrightVoidTeam.BrightVoid)
- Developed a competitive game to encourage accessibility in gaming for the blind.